Finding Aid for the Ronald Bohn Collection of Film and Television Music Sound Recordings PASC-M.0105
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Ragtime, 1981; 1 12" sound disc (Box 145)
  Publisher no.: 5E-565
  Music from the motion picture plus additional music.
- Raiders of the Lost Arc, 1981; 1 12" sound disc (Box 145)
  Publisher no.: AL 37373
- Rambo: First Blood Part II, 1985; 1 12" sound disc (Box 145)
  Publisher no.: STV 81246
- The Razor's Edge, 1984; 1 12" sound disc (Box 145)
  Publisher no.: RS 1009
- Reds, 1981; 1 12" sound disc (Box 145)
  Publisher no.: BJS 37690
- The Reivers, 1 12" sound disc (Box 145)
  Publisher no.: OS 3510
- Remember My Name, 1978; 1 12" sound disc (Box 145)
  Publisher no.: JS 35553
- The Return of a Man Called Horse, 1976; 1 12" sound disc (Box 145)
  Publisher no.: UA-LA692-G
- Risky Business, 1984; 1 12" sound disc (Box 145)
  Publisher no.: V2302
- The River, 1984; 1 12" sound disc (Box 145)
  Publisher no.: MCA-6138
- Rock--a-bye Your Baby, 1977; 1 12" sound disc (Box 147)
  Publisher no.: MCA-2058
  The Jolson story.
- Salvador, 1987; 1 12" sound disc (Box 145)
  Publisher no.: 704.400
- September Song: the Songs of Jimmy Durante, 1963; 1 12" sound disc (Box 149)
  Publisher no.: 1506
- So Many Ways, 1996; 1 12" sound disc (Box 143)
  Publisher no.: 0 85500
  From the High School High soundtrack.
- So Many Ways, 1996; 1 12" Sound Disc (Box 147)
  Publisher no.: 0-85500
- St. Elmo's Fire, 1985; 1 12" sound disc (Box 147)
  Publisher no.: 81261-1-E
- Star Wars: Return of the Jedi, 1983; 1 12" sound disc (Box 145)
  Publisher no.: AGL1-3650
- Stand By Me, 1986; 1 12" sound disc (Box 147)
  Publisher no.: 81677-1-E
- The Stripper: and Other Fun Songs for the Family, 1 12" sound disc (Box 143)
  Publisher no.: Se 4062
  The Stripper -- Night Train -- What is This Thing Called Love -- Mood Indigo -- Banned in Boston -- St. James Infirmary -- Soft Lights and Sweet Music -- Black and Tan Fantasy -- Harlem Nocturne -- Sophisticated Lady -- Blue Prelude -- My Heart Belongs to Daddy.
- Superfly, Shaft, Slaughter and Other Superdudes, 1 12" sound disc (Box 141)
  Publisher no.: SPC 3333
- Swamp Thing, 1982; 1 12" sound disc (Box 146)
  Publisher no.: STV 81154
- Take Me Out to the Ball Game, 1 12" sound disc (Box 145)
- Tap, 1988; 1 12" sound disc (Box 145)
  Publisher no.: SE 45084
- Taxi Driver, 1976; 1 12" sound disc (Box 145)
  Publisher no.: AL 4079
- Tess, 1981; 1 12" sound disc (Box 145)
  Publisher no.: MCA-5193
- That's Entertainment, 1974; 1 12" sound disc (Box 145)
  Publisher no.: MCA2-11002
- That's Entertainment, Part 2, 1985; 1 12" sound disc (Box 145)
  Publisher no.: MCA-6155
- They're Playing Our Song, 1979; 1 12" sound disc (Box 145)
  Publisher no.: NbLP 7141
  The original cast recording.
- They Shoot Horses, Don't They?, 1 12" sound disc (Box 149)
  Publisher no.: ABCS-OC-10
  Musical highlights from the original sound track.
- The 3rd Man. Theme, 1 12" sound disc (Box 145)
  Publisher no.: LL 1560
- Thoroughly Modern Millie, 1 12" sound disc (Box 149)
  Publisher no.: DL 1500
- Those Glorious MGM Musicals, 1973; 2 12" sound discs (Box 148)
  Publisher no.: 2 SES 44 ST
  The Band Wagon -- Kiss Me Kate.
  On container, "2 complete original sound track recordings."
- Three Days of the Condor, Capitol; 1 12" sound disc (Box 145)
  Publisher no.: SW-11489
- Till the Clouds Roll By, 1986; 1 12" sound disc (Box 145)
  Publisher no.: MCA-25000
- A Time to Sing, 1985; 1 12" sound disc (Box 142)
  Publisher no.: MCA 1458
  From the motion picture soundtrack.
- Tony & Strings, 1972; 1 12" sound disc (Box 147)
  Publisher no.: PR 5069 SD
- Tootsie, 1982; 1 12" sound disc (Box 145)
  Publisher no.: 23781-1
- A Tree Grows in Brooklyn, 1 12" sound disc (Box 149)
  Publisher no.: ML 4405
- Trouble in Mind, 1986; 1 12" sound disc (Box 141)
  Publisher no.: 90501-1-E
- True Grit, 1 12" sound disc (Box 146)
  Publisher no.: ST-263
- 12 Inch, 1986; 1 12" sound disc (Box 147)
  Publisher no.: SP-0012
- Ultimo Tango en Paris, 1973; 1 12" sound disc (Box 145)
  Publisher no.: 6269
  On container, "Banda original de sonido de la pelicula."
- Under Fire, 1983; 1 12" sound disc (Box 146)
  Publisher no.: 23965-1
- The Unsinkable Molly Brown, 1986; 1 12" sound disc (Box 145)
  Publisher no.: MCA-25011
- Urn!, 1970; 1 12" sound disc (Box 146)
  Publisher no.: UA-LA303-G
- Vertigo, 1 12" sound disc (Box 145)
  Publisher no.: SRI 75117
  From the original soundtrack.
- The Victors, 1963; 1 12" sound disc (Box 145)
  Publisher no.: SCP 516
- Villa Rides!, 1 12" sound disc (Box 145)
  Publisher no.: DLP 25870
- Vladimir Cosma, 1 12" sound disc (Box 147)
  Publisher no.: CA 681
- Vladimir Cosma, 1 12" sound disc (Box 148)
- The Voices and Drums of Africa, 1 12" sound disc (Box 143)
  Publisher no.: MFS 373
- Wall Street, 1987; 1 12" sound disc (Box 145)
- The Wanderers, 1979; 1 12" sound disc (Box 145)
- The Way We Were, 1974; 1 12" sound disc (Box 145)
  Publisher no.: 32830
- The Way We Were, 1974; 1 12" sound disc (Box 149)
  Publisher no.: KS 32830
- West Side Story, 1969; 1 12" sound disc (Box 145)
  Publisher no.: CAS-2313
- West Side Story, 1973; 1 12" sound disc (Box 145)
  Publisher no.: 32603
- Westworld, 1973; 1 12" sound disc (Box 145)
  Publisher no.: 1SE-47-ST
- When the Boys Meet the Girls, 1986; 1 12" sound disc (Box 145)
  Publisher no.: MCA-25013
- White Nights, 1985; 1 12" sound disc (Box 145)
  Publisher no.: 81273-1-E
- The Wicked Lady, 1983; 1 12" sound disc (Box 146)
  Publisher no.: 80073-1
- William Tell, 1989; 1 12" sound disc (Box 145)
  Publisher no.: V2585
  Original soundtrack to the television series "William Tell".
- Willie Dynamite, 1973; 1 12" sound disc (Box 141)
  Publisher no.: MCA 393
- The Witches of Eastwick, 1987; 1 12" sound disc (Box 141)
- Witness, 1985; 1 12" sound disc (Box 141)
  Publisher no.: STV 81237
- The Wiz, 1978; 2 12" sound disks (Box 146)
  Publisher no.: MCA2-14000
- The Wizard of Oz, 1985; 1 12" sound disc (Box 141)
  Publisher no.: MCA 39046
- Wonderful Town, 1 12" sound disc (Box 141)
  Publisher no.: DL 79010
- Year of the Dragon, 1985; 1 12" sound disc (Box 141)
  Publisher no.: STV 81266
- Yor: the Hunter from the Future, 1983; 1 12" sound disc (Box 141)
  Publisher no.: SCRS 1005
  Original motion picture soundtrack. Additional music by Guido and Maurizio De Angelis.
- You Can't Run Away From It, 1 12" sound disc (Box 141)
  Publisher no.: SMY 1003
  Music from the sound track of the Columbia picture. Songs also composed by Gene DePaul.
- You Light Up My life, 1977; 1 12" sound disc (Box 145)
  Publisher no.: AB 4159
- Young Sherlock Holmes, 1985; 1 12" sound disc (Box 141)
  Publisher no.: MCA 6159
- Young Winston, 1972; 1 12" sound disc (Box 141)
  Publisher no.: SFO 36901
- Zorba, 1 12" sound disc (Box 149)
  Publisher no.: SO 118
- Zorba the Greek, 1 12" sound disc (Box 141)
  Publisher no.: S 4167